原创翻译 双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：丁丁猫哒    斑驳的小屋    嘟嘟矢
■
翻译：haloukeiti    薄荷小瑾    脸盆王子
校对：南鹞北鹰    后期：Sung1219
卢克
Luke!
该你了
You're up next.
该上场了
It's showtime.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentleman.
让你们大饱眼福的疯狂铁网飞车秀
Feast your eyes on the two ton metal mesh of madness.
观众们  他来了
And here he is, folks.
独一无二的梦中情人  潇洒卢克
the one,the only, Handsome Luke and the Heartthrobs.
看他们打破地心引力  展现非凡车技
Watch as they defy gravity and see typical force of 3Gs.
看他们如何骑着摩托
Watch as they ride their
在铁网中翻天覆地  与彼此擦身而过
motorcycles upside down within inches of each other.
速度快得你无法想象
At speeds which you can hardly comprehend.
请大家为他鼓掌
Come on everybody give it up for him.
潇洒卢克
Handsome Luke.
他进去了
There he go folks.
大家给他点鼓励
Come on give them a hand.
开始了  为他们加油
There they go. Come on, get them going.
你们真是好样的
Good work everyone.
潇洒卢克
Handsome Luke.
发动机已经开始旋转
There they go revving them up.
请为他鼓掌  潇洒卢克
Let's here it, come on give him a hand. Handsome Luke.
我得走了
I gotta go.
你还记得我名字吗
Do you remember my name?
罗米娜
Romina.
我喜欢叫你罗
I liked to call you Ro.
你在干什么  有空吗
What are you doing now? You got plans?
我要回家了
I gotta go home.
要我载你一程吗
Want me to give you a ride?
谢谢
Thanks.
你不想跟我说点什么吗
You don't want to talk or anything?
你知道我明天就要走了
You know I leave town tomorrow.
这一走又是一年
After we pack up, I'm not going to be around for another year.
又是一年
Another year?
你想不想...
Hey you wanna...
去喝一杯什么的
get a beer or something?
我有主了  所以
I got someone, so...
不行
No.
我只是想再见见你
I just wanted to see you again.
谢谢
Thanks.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentleman.
有请独一无二的  你们的梦中情人
Introducing the one, the only, Handsome Luke
潇洒卢克
and the Heartthobs.
罗米娜在吗
Is Romina here?
不在
No.
等等
Hold on.
她在上班
She's working.
好吧
Okay.
还记得我吗
Do you remember me?
当然记得
Yes I remember you.
这家伙是谁
Who's that guy?
他是你儿子
He's yours.
你想抱他吗
You want to hold him?
抱好
Here you go.
他叫詹森
His name's Jason.
餐齐了
There you go.
-谢谢  -好吃吗
- Thanks. - Good? Great.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
你有没有话要跟我说
Anything you wanna tell me?
你觉得我走之前是不是该知道些什么
Anything you think I might wanna know before I leave here?
要是我再也不会来了呢
Forever and I never come back?
我们出去说
Let's go outside.
走吧
Come on.
你是不打算告诉我吗
You weren't gonna tell me?
你只是玩玩而已  不是吗
It was just a fling right?
所以你就不需要告诉我吗
That means you don't have to tell me?
哪怕是出于礼貌
Just as a common courtesy or...
没准法律也规定
There might even be a law you know.
你该告诉对方的
You gotta fucking tell somebody.
我这一年都没有你的消息
I haven't heard from you for over a year.
你就这样离开了  连电话都没有
You just took off. Never called me.
还有四个小时我就要走了
I gotta leave in four hours.
我不知道该做什么
I don't know what to do.
你该做什么就做什么
You do whatever you need to do.
你要怎么办
What are you gonna do?
我会做我该做的
I'm gonna do what I have to do.
我要上学
I'm going to school.
照顾詹森  还要工作
I take care of Jason. I work here.
我有男朋友
I have a man.
这就是我要做的  这就是我的生活
So that's what I'm doing. That's my life.
你很忙啊
You're busy?
是啊  我真的很忙
Yeah, yeah I'm real busy.
我不想耽误你
I don't wanna keep you.
好吧
Okay.
Alright.
哪天结工钱  杰克  周五吗
When does this pay period end Jack? On Friday?
怎么了
Why?
我需要钱
Cause I gotta get paid.
先付半周的钱给我好吗
Just pay me for half the week alright?
我从不预支
I don't give advances out.
我不是要预支  杰克
I'm not asking for a advance, Jack.
我不干了
I'm quitting.
-你不能走  -我已经决定了
- You can't quit. - I just did.
你看起来就像个公主
You look like a princess.
你还在这做什么
What are you still doing here?
我走不了了
I stuck around.
你来的不是时候
This is really not a good time.
-我知道  -是啊
- No. - No.
我只是想带他去公园
I was just gonna take him to the park or
或者就在门口坐坐
maybe see if I can just sit on the porch.
跟他打个招呼
Say hi to him.
我们正要去教堂
We're on the way to church.
你要去教堂
You're going to church?
这是科菲
This is Kofi.
-我们该走了  -好的
- We need to go. - Yeah.
你该提前联系我  别这样突然出现
You should call. You just can't show up, you know.
-可以走了吗  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
你住在这吗
You live here?
是啊  这是我家
Yep. This is my house.
你还能在这待多久
How long you in town?
我打算不走了
I'm going to stick around.
你看什么
What are you looking at?
你非要在今天这样干吗
Are you really gonna do this shit today?
干什么
Do what?
以上帝的名义赋予圣水和圣灵
By Gods gift through water and the holy spirit
我们将得以重生  并获得永生
we are reborn to everlasting life.
祈祷上帝能够继续保佑我们
In his goodness may he continue to pour out his blessings
保佑他的儿女们
upon these sons and daughters of his.
让他们成为他忠实的子民
May he make them faithful members of his holy people.
我以圣父  圣子以及圣灵之名
Jason, I baptize you in the name of the father...
为你洗礼  詹森
and of the son and of the holy spirit.
你的儿子已蒙圣恩
This child of yours has been enlighten by Christ.
他已是光明之子
He is to walk always as a child of the light.
我以耶稣教父之名免除你的罪过
By the father of our lord Jesus Christ I free you from sin.
现在我授于你救赎的棱镜
We now anoint you with the prism of salvation
正如耶稣授于牧师  先知与国王
As Christ was anointed priest, prophet, and king.
愿你永远成为他的子民
So may you always live as a member of his body
共享永生  阿门
sharing everlasting life. Amen.
以孩子的名义
In the name of this child.
以子民的名分
In the spirit of a common sonship,
让我们用主所赐之词祈祷
let us pray together in the words our lord has given us.
我们的天主
Our father who art in heaven
愿尔名见圣  愿尔国降临
hallowed be thy name, thy kingdom come
愿尔的旨意奉行在人间  如同行在天上
thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.
感谢主赐予食物  宽恕我们的罪
Give us this day, our daily bread, and forgive us our trespasses
如同我们宽恕他人的罪
as we forgive those who trespass against us
让我们远离诱惑与邪恶
and lead us not into temptation but delivery us from evil.
愿万能的主  圣父  圣子
The almighty God, the father, the son,
圣灵  保佑你  阿门
and the holy spirit bless you. Amen.
现在  就让我们欢迎
Now as we receive our new member
这位教会的新成员
into our parish, let us all welcome him with great joy.
你骑得真好
You ride that thing really good.
非常好
Really good.
骑得真不错
You ride good, man.
要我载你回城吗
You like a ride into town?
你可以省点油
Save you some gas, man.
你是路过这里吗
Just passing through?
我刚在这落脚
I'm just settling in.
-你住哪儿  -某个该死的汽车旅馆
- Where you staying? - Some fucking motel.
是啊  附近没一家好的
Yeah, they're no good around here.
整个镇子的都烂的像屎一样
Whole towns gone to shit, man.
找到工作了吗
So you got a job?
还没
No.
引擎方面你在行吗
You know your way around an engine?
还行
Yeah.
我有家修理店  在玛莎路
Cause I got a, I got shop. A repair shop on Marsha Road.
来看看吧  我正好缺人手
Come check it out man. I could always use a good worker.
好的
Alright.
不是很大  但
It ain't much. It's...
这是我自己的店
what it is you know. It's mine.
没人能解雇我
No one can kick me out of it.
那是工作车间
So it's a workshop in there.
它叫图尔
This is Tour.
我这的活儿不是很多
I don't get a whole lot of work here you know.
但是如果你觉得不够的话
But if you want you can look for other jobs
你可以去找别的活儿
or whatever you know if it's not enough for you.
我什么都做
I do everything.
只要是关于汽车的我都能做
Everything there is to do to a car I know how to do.
你不会的我可以教你
Anything you don't know, I can teach you, you know.
下面还有一辆房车
And I got a trailer down here.
愿意的话就留下来吧
Stay there if you want.
它害羞了
See she's shy.
去哪儿了  球呢
Where is it? Where's the ball?
拖车在那儿
There's the trailer.
-它捡到了吗  -它才不会去捡的
- Did she get it? - No, she ain't gonna get it.
你一直一个人住吗
Do you live out here all alone?
是的  一个人住
Yeah, I live alone.
有时候会有人来待一阵
But sometimes people come stay for a while, you know.
就这些了  这里虽然小
That's it. It's not much, but you know
但是什么都有
it got whatever you need in there.
你一定很孤单
You must get lonely.
罗伯  不是我不领情
Look, Rob. I don't want to be ungrateful.
我很感激你这么帮我
I really appreciate what you're doing for me and shit,
但是我他妈的需要赚很多钱
but I got to make more fucking money.
老兄  要是能多给你点  我一定给
Hey man, if I could pay you more, I would, you know.
你那么在行  真的太厉害了
Youre good at what you do man. Really good.
我能修好那辆老麦克卡车
I could fix up that old Mack truck
你停在草坪上的当摆设的那辆
that's sitting there like your goddamn lawn ornament.
要是你能修好就太好了
That's good you can go ahead and
但是我没有钱付你
fix it up but I don't have the money to pay you.
你还可以干别的事情
You know, there are other things that can be done, you know.
比如
Like what?
我们可以去抢银行
We could rob a bank.
-尽胡说八道  -我没有胡说八道
- You're full of shit. - I'm not full of shit.
我抢过四次  都是十二年前的事了
I've done it four times myself and stopped twelve years ago.
当时这事可火了
It was getting too hot.
只要别做太多次  就没事
As long as you don't do it too many times, you're fine.
你有孩子吗  你想养他吗
You got a kid? You want to provide for that kid?
你要打败你的对手吗
You want to maybe edge out your competition?
你得利用你的优势
You got to do that using you're skill set.
而你的优势
And your skill set...
很特别
very unique.
你觉得怎么样
What do you say?
-去你妈的  -好吧
- Go fuck yourself. - Okay.
那就用你那微薄的收入去养家吧
Well, good luck supporting your family on minimum wage.
他是我儿子  我要留在他身边
He's my son and I should be around him.
我没有父亲  所以变成现在这样子
I wasn't around my dad and look the fucking way I turned out.
我想照顾你
Look, I wanna take care of you.
我想照顾我儿子  这是我的责任
I want to take care of my son. That's my job.
让我尽我的责任
Let me do my job.
好吧  那你拿什么来照顾我们呢
Okay, how how are you gonna take care of us?
别这样说
Don't say it like that.
-那你怎么照顾我呢  -别
- But how are you gonna take care of me? - Don't...
别挖苦我
Don't talk down to me.
这是一个问题  我没有挖苦你
It's a question. I'm not talking down to you.
-我只是问问  -我会想办法的
- It's just a question. - I'll find... find a way to do it.
你想要房子吗  我会给你房子
You want a house? I'll get you a house.
你想离开这吗  那就走吧
You wanna get the fuck outta here? Get outta here.
我有个房车
I got that trailer.
再弄辆卡车  我们就可以上路了
I'll get a truck. We'll hit the road.
你想去哪儿  我们就在哪儿停
You pick a place you like? We'll stop.
你不想待在这  那我们就离开这里
You don't wanna be there? Fuck you we're outta there.
那我妈妈怎么办
What about my mom?
她可以跟我们一起
She can come.
-科菲呢  -他就不用了
- What about Kofi? - He can stay.
他可以再找个女孩  有自己的孩子
He can get his own girl and his own kid.
这是每个人该有的权利
That's every man's right.
-听起来真是个美梦  -罗
- Sounds like a nice dream. - Ro.
如果必要的话  你可以用这个
You can umm... use this if you wanna.
但是记住  我抢了四次都没用
But keep in mind that I did four banks with a note.
换句话说  其实你不需要带枪
In other words you don't need the gun.
我不喜欢用枪  他们都是平民百姓
I never liked guns man. They're vulgar.
也许你想带着
But you may want to take it.
不管你想怎么干  我都不会带
I don't... whatever you wanna do.
我们怎么做
How do we do it?
首先  我们一早就要去  穿得像样点
Okay, first thing is we're gonna go in there nice and early.
一开门就要去  明白吗
Just when the doors open okay?
观察所有的柜员
You're gonna take a look at all the tellers...
找一个年纪最大的女人下手
Go for the oldest woman you can alright.
没有的话就找一个看起来最温顺的
Failing that, go to the most meek.
让她把钱放在桌子上  为什么呢
Get her to put the money out on the table. Why?
这样你就能知道里面有没有染色包
So that way you can see if there's a dye pack.
染色包  会把钱永久地染成鲜红色  警告人们这些钱是偷来的
把钱装进包里  别留下任何东西
You put it in your pocket. You don't hand anything over to them.
不用掏枪  直接走人
You don't show them the gun. And you go.
骑上摩托车  我在四条街外接你
Get on your bike. I'll be about four blocks away.
把摩托车开进卡车
Ride it into the truck.
然后我们回家就成了  我们就有钱了
Bam we're home, we're done, we're rich.
你把车停在路边
What happens if you get stopped
把货箱门开着没事吗
sitting by the side of the road with a open cube truck.
你要怎么说
What are you gonna say?
-什么意思  -假设我是警察
- What do you mean what I'm gonna do? - I'm a officer.
先生  你把货箱门开着干嘛
Excuse me, sir. What are you doing with a open cube truck?
你在这做什么  为什么要停在这
What are you doing? Why are you sitting here like this?
我的车坏了  我在等人来修
Oh I'm broken down. I'm waiting for the, you know, repairs.
谢谢关心  警官
Thank you for asking officer.
-回答得很好  -是吧
- That's a nice touch. - Right.
要是你屁股长了癣
What are you gonna do if you get jock itch and you know you...
你必须以90英里的时速在街上狂飙
you're riding ninty miles a hour down the street.
你还是会骑的是吧
You're gonna keep riding right?
我是说我们得各司其职
Yeah? I mean we do what we do.
要是我们联手的话  就无敌了
But when we do it together? Pssshh... Shazam.
我只是说说
I'm just saying.
自从霍哈二重唱后就没有这样的团队了
Not since Hall and Oates, has there been such a team.
霍哈二重唱  美国老牌流行摇滚乐团
你想当哪个  我知道了
Which one do you... Oh, I know.
所以我是黑卷发的那个
So I got to be the dark curly hair guy?
你是长得帅的那个  这样就对了
You got to be the good looking one? I guess that's about right.
我们一定能成的  你会爱上这行的
This is going to be good. You're going to like doing this.
这是你人生最大一搏
Biggest rush of your life.
想活命的就把手举起来
Everybody who wants to live put your hands in the fucking air!
都给我过来  过来
Get over here! Get over here now!
快他妈给我过来  跪下
Get the fuck over here! Get on your knees!
你叫什么
Alright, what's your name?
-马克斯  -马克斯是我的小狗
- Max. - Max is my little fucking dog.
现在他就要去收你们的钱
If by get your fucking money and he's going to fetch.
快点拿出来放到桌子上  快点
Get it out and put it on the table right now! Get it out!
祈祷
Pray!
快祈祷
让我听到你们的祷告
Let me here you fucking pray!
把钱都拿出来了吧
Got that money out boy?
去拿其他地方的  快点
Go fucking fetch. Fast!
都拿来  放到这个包里
Get it up. Put it in that bag.
他们没掉头
They're not turning!
拿了多少钱
How much did you get?
包里的
Bag.
噢  宝贝
Oh baby. Oh.
太棒了  做的太他妈好了
Beautiful. Fucking baby, boy!
你没事吧  你还好吗
Are you okay man? You good?
你成功了
You did it man!
成功了
You did it!
好样的  我们成功了
Yeah man! We fucking did it!
我们他妈的成功了
We fucking did it!
我在夜里醒来
I get up in the evening
感觉无话可说
And I ain't got nothing to say
我在早晨到家
I come home in the moring
睡去感受依然
I go to bed feeling the same way
我就是有点累
I ain't nothing but tired
我就是累了  对自己倦了
Man, I'm just tired and bored with myself
嘿  宝贝
Hey there, baby
我需要点帮助
I could use just a little help
如果你要生火
You can't start a fire
怎能没有火星
You can't start a fire without a spark
我们需要租枪
This gun's for hire
即使我们只是在黑暗中起舞
even if we're just dancing in the dark
跟我讲讲他吧
Tell me about him.
他喜欢吃什么
What's he like eat?
他喜欢  很喜欢吃苹果
He like, really likes apples.
虽然都是我嚼过才喂给他
Though I kind of have to chew it up for him.
-你给他嚼苹果  -是啊
- You chew up his apple? - Yeah.
听着挺恶心  但我喂他时不觉得
It sounds gross but it's not when I'm doing it.
他吃过冰淇淋吗
Has he ever had ice cream?
还没
Not yet.
开玩笑吧
You fucking kidding me?
-他还太小  -胡扯
- He's still a baby. - Bullshit.
你这当的什么家啊
What kind of house are you running?
连冰淇淋都没有
No ice cream.
为什么他不能吃冰淇淋呢
Why can't he have that?
不是他不能吃  只是还没让他吃
It's not like he can't have any. He just hasn't had it.
我可以给他吃冰淇淋吗
Can I give it to him?
-你想给他冰淇淋吃  -是的
- You want to give him ice cream? - Yeah.
我想跟他一起做些他还没做过的事
I want to do something with him that's his first time.
他吃冰淇淋的时候我想看着他的脸
I want to look at his face when he tries ice cream.
以后他每次吃冰淇淋的时候
Every time he has ice cream for the rest of his life,
我都要让他看到我的脸
he's going to see my fucking face.
-得了吧  -他真的太好玩了
- Okay, come on. - Ah, he's really funny.
得了吧
Come on.
想听听摩托车发动的声音吗
Want to hear it on?
好了  惊喜吧  他经常哭
Okay, surprise. He cries a lot.
先生  要我把摩托车也拍进去吗
Hola senor, you want the bike in it too?
所有的  别说出来  尽管拍
Yeah, just all, you don't say. Just capture the mood.
-车子真不错  -车是我们家庭的一员
- It's a nice bike. - Bike's part of the family.
再来一张吧
You want another one?
你确定要在她哭的时候拍吗
You sure I should take it when she's crying?
好
Okay.
这个戏法不错
That's a good trick.
把钱都放到柜台上
Put that fucking money on the counter.
把真钱给我
Give me the real stuff.
别拿假的糊弄我  我分得清真假
Don't give me the fucking fake stuff. I know what it is.
操  过来  过来
Shit. Come here. Come here.
这是什么啊
What is this?
-这是什么  -礼物
- What is this? - It's presents.
-天啊  这是什么  -是个婴儿床
- Oh my God. What is that? - It's a crib.
慢点  慢点  慢点
Easy, easy, easy.
老大  你别动  要不就掉下去了
Boss, you gotta stay. You're gonna fall of this bed.
好了
There you go.
妈妈回来了
Your mom's home.
-妈妈  -你觉得她会生气吗
- Hi, mama. - You think she's gonna be mad?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我给他买了个婴儿床和一些玩具
I got him a crib and some toys.
你这么做真的太好了
You know this is really nice and all,
但是你...你得离开
but you gotta,you gotta get this outta here.
你不能这么随便就来这里
You can't just show up like this.
-为什么  -因为这是科菲家
- Why? - Cause this is Kofi's fucking house.
你快走吧
Just get it out, please.
他不能在床上睡
He can't be sleeping in a bed.
会摔下来受伤的  他需要有个婴儿床
He's going to roll out and bust his head open. He needs a crib.
怎么回事
What's going on?
他这样你没意见吗
You okay with this?
我在跟你说话呢  他这样行吗
I'm talking to you. You okay with this?
科菲  他是孩子的爸爸
Kofi, it's his father.
在我们家吗
In our house?
他甚至可以在你不在家的时候就来这里
He's gonna roll up in here even when your not in the house?
-你在这干什么呢  伙计  -嘘
- What are you doing here man? - Shhh.
我在给他做...
I'm making him pr...
别嘘我  这是在我家
Don't shhh me, your in my house man.
你现在就收拾你这些东西马上走
You need to pack all this shit up and get out the house, man.
你觉得自己是谁啊
I don't know who you think you are
闯入我们的生活
just coming up in our life and
随便做改动  这样行不通的
changing shit around but this ain't going to work.
-声音小点  -你说什么
- You gotta lower your voice man. - Excuse me?
声音小点
Lower your voice.
罗米娜  你能不能出去一下
Romina can you, can you step outside please?
收拾好东西滚吧
Pack all this shit up and take it out, man.
-你都把孩子弄哭了  -是你弄哭的
- You're making the baby cry. - You're making the baby cry.
收拾好东西  立刻离开这
Pick this shit up and get it out of the house now, man.
我不想跟你废话
I'm not fucking with you.
收拾你这些破玩意儿  滚蛋
Pick up all this shit. Fuck you man.
科菲
Kofi.
科菲  宝贝
Kofi. Baby.
-妈妈  -科菲
- Mommy! - Kofi!
科菲
Kofi.
宝贝
Baby.
-宝贝  -放开我
- Baby. - Get off of me.
你个疯子  你他妈就是个疯子
You're crazy! You're fucking crazy!
出去  滚出去  滚
Get out! Get out! Get out!
拜托了  别  别
Please, please, please. No, no, no.
打电话叫救护车
Call an ambulance.
好的
Okay.
没事的
It's okay.
都结束了
It's over.
-你叫卢克・格兰顿吗  -是的
- Is your name Luke Glanton? - Yes.
格兰顿先生  有人提交申请报告
Mr. Glanton, a complain has been filed
指控你犯有二级攻击罪
it alleges assault in the second degree
这在纽约州是一项重罪
which is a felony in the state of New York.
若有人提出此项控诉
When such a complain is filed,
你有权申请休庭以聘请律师
you have the right to an adjournment to obtain a lawyer.
辩方律师  你想
Counselor do you wish to
放弃提询听证吗
waive any further reading of the arraignment?
法官大人  我代表我方当事人
Would your honor, on behalf of my client,
进行无罪辩护
I enter a not guilty plea.
根据我对被告人历史的了解
Given the history that I am aware of this defendant and
以及相关指控
as well the allegations,
我将保释金额定为2500美元
I'm going to set bail in the amount of $2,500.
可以提交现金也可以通过保释代理人提交
Bail may be posted either in cash or by bail bondsman.
与此同时  我将签署临时令
In the mean time I will issue the temporary order of protection
被告人不得进行暴力
requiring this defendant to refrain from violent,
攻击性  进攻性  或是
offensive, assaultive, or
骚扰行为  同时远离申请人
harassing conduct, and to remain away from the complainee.
这是你的钱  谢谢你赎我出来
There's your money. Thanks for bailing me out.
我想一天干两票
I want to do two in one day.
我想先抢布兰迪万街的塔斯科银行
I want to do the Trustco on Brandywine.
等所有的条子都来追我的时候
When all those fucking pigs are coming after me
我就把钱扔给他们  然后去鹿特丹大街
I'm going to split out the back. I wanna go down to Rotterdam
在第一国家银行干一票
and I want to do that First National.
卢克  如果你的车速快似闪电
You know something Luke, if you ride like lightning,
那么你的坠亡则迅若惊雷
you're going to crash like thunder.
我不能让你把我们两个都拉下水
I'm not going to let you bring us both down.
胡扯  别磨磨唧唧的
Fuck that, don't be such a fucking pussy.
不  结束了
No, man, it's over.
我干不了  也绝不会干
I can't do it. Won't do it.
-你自己做决定  -操
- You made your fucking choice. - Fuck you!
听着  如果你今晚要出去
Hey, you know what? If you go out tonight,
把车开走  你会更不引人注意
take the truck. It'll be less visible.
我只能帮你到这了
Last favor I'll do you.
我退出了
I'm done.
你他妈不干了
You're fucking done?
-是的  -你真不干了
- Yeah. - You're done?
都结束了
It's over.
如果我跪下乞求你
If I got on my knees and I pleaded with you
别离开我  留在我怀里
Not to go, but to stay in my arms
你会不会走出门去
Would you walk out the door
就像你上次那样
Like you did once before
但是这次请你留下
This time, be different, please stay
别离开我
Don't go
如果我祷告你的名字
If I call out your name like a prayer
你还会让我独自流泪吗
Would you leave me alone with my tears
你懂的  我如此需要你
Knowing I, I need you so
罗
Ro.
拿着这个  把这个拿上
Just take this. Just take it.
罗  对不起  我就是个疯子
Ro, I'm sorry. I'm a fucking maniac.
罗
Ro.
-能让我上车吗  -你拿着这个
- Can I get in the car, please? - Just take this.
你不爱我  也不喜欢我
You don't love me. You don't like me.
我都懂  我就是垃圾
Man, I fucking get it. I'm a piece of shit.
好吗
Okay?
我还是孩子的父亲  我可以给他些东西
I'm still his father. I can give him stuff.
这是我给他的  交给他
I got this for him. Just give it to him.
告诉他是我给的
Tell him it's from me.
如果我用歌声呼唤你的名
If I called out your name like a song,
那是只为你写的歌
That was written for you, you alone
你永远也别想再见到他
You're never going to see him again.
请把这个给他
Please give that to him.
别离开我  请留下来
Don't go, please stay
亲爱的  你是我永远的爱
You know I always love you, darling
请留下来
Please stay
-嘿  -没事的
- Hi. - Hey, it's okay.
没事
It's alright.
-张嘴  -为什么
- Open your mouth. - Why?
因为你欠我一辆新车
You owe me a new bike.
-对吧  -是的
- Right? - Yeah.
钱在哪里  给我
Where's that good one? Give it to me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
操
Fuck.
该死的玻璃
Fucking glasses.
他妈的
Shit!
他妈的蠢货
Fucking idiot.
操  该死的上帝
Oh shit. Fucking Christ.
所有人他妈的趴到地上
Everybody get down on the fucking floor!
你  起来
You! Get up!
他妈的站起来
Get the fuck up!
把包里装满钱
Fill up that fucking bag full of money.
别看我  举起...脸朝地
Don't look at me, put your... No faces!
你  起来
You! Get up!
-我正在站起来  -站起来
- I'm getting up. - Get up!
把钱
Get the fuck...
把钱取出来
Get that fucking money...
-把钱拿过来  -好的  别冲动
- Put that fucking money in there! - Okay, stay calm.
你在干什么  扔过来
What are you doing? Throw it over!
-对不起  我  -扔过来
- I'm sorry, I'm... - Throw it over!
对不起  抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
那个男的哪儿去了  小子
Where's that guy back there? There was a fucking guy. Hey guy!
-站起来  -好
- Get up! - Alright.
把包扔过来  你最好能顺利扔过来
Throw that over. You better not fuck this up.
老天爷
Jesus Christ!
这个破玩意儿
This fucking shit.
趴下
Get the fuck down!
操
Shit!
混蛋  混蛋
Fuck you. Fuck you.
混蛋
Fuck you.
105  我在追捕抢劫嫌犯
105, in pursuit of robbery suspect.
在布兰迪万北街
North on Brandywine.
黑色连体裤  黑色头盔
Black jumpsuit. Black helmet.
105  嫌犯拐入威尔墓园
105, suspect taking a turn into Vale cementary.
我在威尔墓园追捕摩托大盗
In Vale cementary, in pursuit of suspect on motorcycle.
向摩耶逊街方向行进
Going towards Moyerson.
嫌犯摩托车疑似后胎没气了
Appears to have a flat on rear tire.
他离开摩耶逊街  转向斯代特街
He's heading out of Moyerson. He's heading toward State.
在斯代特街截住他
Cut him off on State.
嫌犯在斯代特街被障碍物挡住
Got him blocked at barricade at State Street.
嫌犯摔倒  嫌犯摔倒
Suspect is down, suspect is down,
嫌犯  嫌犯驶向斯代特街
suspect... suspect is going down State Street.
他在摩耶逊街的巴里商店附近
He got around the Barri's on Moyerson.
从摩耶逊街向南  向斯代特街行进
Heading south on Moyerson. Heading towards State.
在去往普利茅斯方向的路上
In course to Plymouth.
确认嫌犯一个车胎漏气
Suspect does have a flat tire.
104  我看到辆摩托车驶向埃尔默街
104, I got a visual of motorcycle heading south on Elmer.
在斯坦福以西
West on Stanford.
向着普利茅斯以北前进
He's heading north on Plymouth.
蹲下
Stay down!
徒步追踪
In foot pursuit.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
过来  到这来  家里只有你们吗
Come here! Come here! Are you the only ones here?
-是的  -过来
- Yeah. - Come here.
-滚过来  -好
- Get the fuck over here! - Okay.
我不会伤害你们的  上楼
I'm not going to hurt you. Just get upstairs.
上楼
Get upstairs!
我在普利茅斯街702号
I'm at 702 Plymouth.
我需要支援到房子的东南角进行支援
I need a backup unit for the southeast corner of the house...
我在西北角警戒
I have the northwest corner secured.
蹲那儿别动
Get down over there.
妈的
Fuck.
出去
Get out of here.
趴下  趴到地上  趴到地上
Get down! Get down on the ground. Get down on the ground.
房子里还有别人吗
Is anybody else inside?
有  他在楼上
Yes, he's upstairs.
警察
Police!
罗  罗  别挂电话
Ro? Ro, don't hang up.
我现在有麻烦了
I'm in trouble.
我在  我在一个女人家
I'm... I'm in some lady's house.
罗  你能帮我个忙吗
Ro, would you do a favor for me, please?
只帮这一次  我再也不会求你了
Just one thing and I'll never ask for anything again.
警察
Police!
别跟宝宝讲我的事好吗
Look, don't tell him about me, okay?
警察
Police!
把枪放下
Put your gun down!
-可以吗  -警察
- Okay? - Police!
就地趴下
Lay down on your stomach
两手张开  面向房门
with your hands spread apart face right the door.
罗
Ro?
-罗  拜托了  -警察  放下
- Ro. please... - Police, drop your....
104  我在普利茅斯街702号
104, on 702 Plymouth.
有交火  嫌犯受伤
Shots fired. Perps down.
我被击中了
I've been shot.
请派一个小分队到普利茅斯街702号
Send a box to 702 Plymouth.
-举起手来  -马上举起手来
- Show me your fucking hands! - Get those fucking hands up now!
-举起手来  -举起手来
-Get your hands up now! -Get your hands up now!
马上把手举起来
Get the fucking hands up right now!
克莱德  你还好吗  没事吧
Clyde, you alright? You okay?
我逮住他了  我逮住他了
I got him, I got him....
-上上上  -别动
- Go, go, go. - Do not move.
请再派一名警察过来
Give me another cop back here.
亲爱的
Baby?
我老爸怎么也来了
What's my dad doing here?
我们都来了
We're all here.
你还记得发生了什么吗  记得吗
Do you remember what happened? Any of it?
亲爱的  别想了  别想了
Okay honey, don't, don't.
没事  没关系
It's alright, it's alright.
别这样  别弄了
Don't do that. Leave it.
-亲爱的  别  -艾弗里
- Hey, hey, hey, honey. Just can't... - Avery...
宝贝
Hey, honey.
-艾弗里  -艾弗里
- Avery! - Avery!
你受伤严重  不能激动
You got a bad injury. You gotta take it easy.
没事了  宝贝  你要放松
It's okay, honey, you just gotta relax okay.
-我们都在这里  -你还好吗
- We're all here. - You alright?
-好  好  没事  -明白吗
- Okay, okay, yeah. - You understand?
明白
Yeah.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-很抱歉  -没关系
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
我们都在  没事了  没事了
Hey we're all here. It's okay, it's okay.
-嗯  好的  -没事了
- Yeah, yeah. - It's okay.
你得在医院住几天
You're going to be in there a couple of days alright.
只是住几天而已
That's it. A couple of days.
克罗斯先生  早上好
Good morning, Mr. Cross.
你有几个访客
You feeling up to a couple of visitors?
有几个人想要跟你聊聊
There's a couple of men who want to speak to you.
艾弗里
Avery.
我们的英雄怎么样了
How's our hero?
-局长  -感觉怎么样  没事了吧
- Chief. - How you feeling? You alright?
医院照顾得好吗
They taking good care of you?
很好  长官  谢谢关心
Good. Yeah, yeah, yes sir. Thank you.
萨巴泰洛来的香肠和胡椒
Sausage and pepper from Sabatellos.
谢谢你来  你好吗
Thanks for coming down. How are you?
我是比尔・金库伦  地方检察官
Bill Killcullen, D.A.
我是艾弗里・克罗斯  很高兴见到你
Avery Cross, nice to meet you.
当然  我认识你
Yeah of course. I know who you are.
我认识你父亲
I know your father, you know.
-很久了  -不好意思
- Long time now. - I apologize.
不不不  他是个好人
No, no, no, he's a great guy.
我相信他儿子更青出于蓝的
I wouldn't have expected anything less from his son.
你超出了我的期望
This was ah, above and beyond.
不  我只是做了常人会做的事
Ah no, I just did what anybody would do.
-对  -对  这样更好
- Yeah. - That's right. And better.
不知道我能不能...
I don't know if I could...
全员都被你鼓舞了
The whole force is pulling for you man.
别忘了  他们都在外面
Don't you forget that. They're all outside.
打着横幅之类的
Banners and everything.
那个人如何了
What happened to that guy?
没了  他死了  结束了
That guys gone. He's dead. It's over.
都是这样的
It's the way it happens.
-对吧  -但他有留下什么人吗
- Right? - Yeah, but did he leave anybody behind?
那不是你现在该担心的
That's not, it's not for you to worry about right now.
我们有人会来跟你谈这个
We got people who are going to talk to you about that.
有人跟他的家人谈话
There's people talking to his family.
又搞定个坏人  你成了英雄
Got rid of another bad guy. And you're a hero.
-对吧  -对
- Alrighty? - Yeah.
比尔想问你几个问题  行吗
Bill wants to ask you a few questions. That alright?
第一反应之类的就行
Just your first impressions, that kind of thing, you know.
-我只想  -明白程序吗
- I just wa.... - Formalities, you know?
-嗯  很简单  -没错
- Yeah, it's pretty simple. -Sure.
-嗯  -我先走了  你们相互熟悉吧
- Yeah. - Alright, I'll leave you to it, get to know each other.
-好吧  -好的
- Alright. - Alright.
那你在门外时怎么了
So what happen when you were just outside the door?
我说  警察  放下武器
Um, I said "Police uh, drop your weapon."
双手分开  趴在地上
Um, "Face down on the ground with your hand spread."
-没有回音  -没有吗
- And uh, nothing. - Nothing?
没有
Nothing.
-你又喊了一次吗  -没有
- Did you announce yourself again or not? - No.
没  我们只需要自报家门吧
No. That's all we need to do is make ourselves known right?
对  但有时很难确认
Yeah. But it's sometimes not easy to
他们是否听见你自报家门了
tell whether if they've heard you making yourself known.
明白我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
反正你喊了  对吧
Anway, you were yelling, is that right?
我按照训练那样
I was making myself known
-自报了家门  -好  好的
- as we were trained, correct. - Okay. Alright.
好  然后呢
Okay. Then what?
这时我知道我得冲进去
At that point I knew I had
我就把门踹开了
to make entry and I kicked the door down.
-门锁了吗  -锁了
- Was the door, was the door locked? - Correct.
你怎么知道的
And you knew that because?
-什么意思  -你假设门上锁了吗
- What do you mean? - Did you assume that the door was locked?
-我怎么知道门锁了吗  -对
- How did I know it was locked? - Yeah.
这个问题是陷阱吗
Is that a trick question?
没有  我只想知道你为什么没拧把手
No, no. I'm just wondering why you didn't turn the thing.
我拧了才知道门锁了的
That's how I know it was locked.
你告诉我了吗
Did you tell me that?
-没有  -好吧
- No. - Okay.
-然后你破门而入了  -对
- Alright, so you kick it in? - Right.
你为什么过来呢
Why are why... why did you come down here?
抱歉  我为什么来呢
I'm sorry, why did I come down here?
对  为什么不是别人
Yeah, why wasn't it somebody else?
办公室里没意思吗
Slow day at the office?
不
No.
那之后呢
What happened after that?
你想我跟你说什么
What would you like me to tell you?
-我只想你告诉我真实情况  -是吗
- I just need you to tell me what happened? - You do?
我不想你记错
I don't want you to misremember, so tomorrow
明天你还得回忆今天是怎么想的
you're trying to match what have you have thought today.
我只想你告诉我看见什么记得什么
I only want you to tell me what you saw, what you remember?
我射中了罪犯  他从窗户跌了下去
I shot the perpetrator. He fell out the window.
我知道  他什么时候开得枪
I know that. When did he pull his gun?
他先还是你先
Did you shoot him first or did he shoot first?
别耍我  好好做事
Don't fuck with me. Do the right thing.
告诉我到底发生了什么
Tell me what the fuck happened.
事情发生得很迅速
It was pretty quick.
谁先开枪的
Who shot first?
他举起手  你就开火了
His hand comes up. You fire.
他举起手了  他开枪  你开枪
His hand comes up. He fires. You fire.
-对  -那样吗
- Right. - Like that?
-嗯  -啪啪两下就结束了
- Yeah. - Like pop, pop.
听起来是他先开枪的
That sounds like he shot first.
对
Yeah.
今天就是艾弗里・克罗斯警官康复的日子
It's just a triumphant day for officer Avery Cross.
他恢复得很好
He left Ellis hospital
从埃利斯医院出院  很高兴幸存了下来
well enough to go home and happy to be alive.
随着斯克奈塔第区的大家族的喝彩
With supporters from his Schenectady PD family cheering him on,
他的父亲  州最高法院法官
His father, State Supreme Court Judge
阿尔・克罗斯表示他很高兴儿子幸存下来
Al Cross says he's very happy his son is alive today.
这是警察的生活  我儿子选择的生活
It's the life of a cop. A life my son chose.
在撞见可疑的摩托车抢匪时
Twenty nine year old Cross hasn't even been on the force for a
29岁的克罗斯入职还未满一年
full year before he ran head on into the alleged Moto Bandit.
在一起银行抢劫后
Pursuing Luke Glanton through
沿斯克奈塔第街追捕卢克・格兰顿
the streets of Schenectady after a bank robbery.
格兰顿跑进一住户家
Glanton ran into a home.
而后与克罗斯警官起了正面冲突
Then he came face to face with Officer Cross.
格兰顿朝克罗斯开枪  射中了他的膝盖
Glanton fired at Cross, hitting him in the knee.
克罗斯反击  击毙格兰顿并解救了人质
Cross fired back. Killing Glanton and saving the hostages.
格兰顿是个流浪汉
Glanton was a drifter
有时也表演摩托车特技
and at times a motorcycle stunt rider.
警察称他有非常暴力的案底
Police say he had a very violent past.
他有一长串的犯罪记录
The guy had a long track record, you know.
他是一名职业罪犯
He was a professional criminal.
去年春天他搬到这里
He moved here last spring and it hasn't
不到一个月就开始抢银行
been a full month before he started robbing banks here.
他留下一个襁褓中的儿子
He leaves behind an infant son.
下一段...
Coming up....
可怕吗  亲爱的
Was it scary, honey?
一切发生得太快
It happened so fast.
没时间害怕
I don't think there was time to be scared.
为我害怕吧
Scary for me.
我就是不懂你为什么这样  没人这样
I just don't understand why you're doing this. Nobody does.
做什么  我怎么了
Doing what? What... what... what am I doing?
我跟你父亲谈了  我们...
I was speaking with your father and we...
-我们都同意  -他当然同意
- We both agree. - Of course... of course... of course he does.
抱歉我刚看到
I'm sorry I just saw...
我是名警察  珍  警察
I'm a cop, Jen, I'm a cop.
我只是觉得经过这次你会受够了
I just thought maybe after this maybe you would have had enough.
-仅此而已  -没什么好谈的
- That's all. - Hey, there's no more to discuss.
我只是觉得这已经够了
I just thought maybe it would have been enough.
仅此而已  好吗
That's it. Okay?
我不可能不那么想
You...you can't expect me not to think that.
你们就是不懂
You guys just don't get it.
对不起  我们只是担心
I'm sorry. We're just worried.
只是担心你  仅此而已
We're just worried about you. That's all.
别这么说了
Stop saying that.
别他妈说了
Stop fucking saying that.
你脑袋里一直在重演整件事吗
Have you been replaying the incident in your mind?
没有
Not really.
没有  我只有试着
Nah, I just try to...
把它从脑袋里清除出去
I'm trying to uh put it out of my mind I think.
有用吗
Does that work?
有用
Yeah.
你觉得自己可以重回岗位了吗
You think you're ready to go back to duty?
可以了
Yes.
你想自己成为警队的一份子吗
Would you want yourself as a partner?
当然
Absolutely.
枪击后你都在想什么
What have you been thinking about since the shooting?
没想什么
Not much, um...
一切都那么疯狂
Have... has... everything's been so crazy, you know.
恢复的事加上
With the rehabilitation and the...
工作  还有家里的一切
work and everything at home.
家里的一切吗
Everything at home?
家里怎么了
What's happening at home?
我回家住了
Well, I'm there now.
-家里很不一样了  -家里都有谁
- It's just much different. - Who's at home with you?
岳母
Well, ah my mother in law ah.
我老婆和儿子
My wife and my boy.
有些...
So there's um...
对我老婆来说  这事太震惊了
You know its been hard on my... my wife. It's a shock.
每天忙孩子的事都对她都没帮助
And an um... it doesn't help that there's a baby around.
但没事  都还行
But it's okay. I mean it's okay.
忙孩子的事都对她没帮助
What do you mean that it doesn't help
是什么意思
that there's a baby around?
我的意思是
Well I just mean that
发生的...这一切
with everything that's... that's going on...
我们都在试着...恢复正常
We're justing trying to... to get all this in order.
在我能处理之前
Before I can take care of that.
这样做很难
It... it's been hard. It... it... it...
我一直忙着
I've just been so busy that it's been...
很难
hard to uh...
看到我的儿子
I've... I've hard time...
我就不好过
looking at my son.
-这是枪击后开始的吗  -嗯
- And that's something new since the shooting? - Mmhm.
我看到警方记录
You know I... I saw in the police
他也有个一岁大的儿子
record that this perp also had a one year old son.
叫做詹森  你一直在想这个吗
His name is Jason. You been thinking about this?
就是说...
This you mean...
-他有孩子影响了我吗  -对
- The fact that he had a boy? - Yeah.
你觉得
Do you think...
你看到儿子就难过是因为
you're having a hard time looking at your son because...
你想到另一个孩子
you're thinking about this
失去了父亲吗
other little boy that won't have his father?
-在等人吗  -没有  你呢
- You expecting somebody? - No. You?
你好吗
How you doing?
-你们好吗  -大家进来吧
- Hey, hows the gimp doing? - Hey, come on in guys.
不了  我们就是来瞧瞧你们
Nah we're just coming in here
看看你们好不好
to check up on you and see how you're doing.
你好吗  珍
Hi, how are you, Jen?
很好  你呢  斯科特
I'm good. How are you, Scotty?
很好  我挺好的
Oh I'm alright. I'm doing good.
-比他强  -他没事
- Better than this guy. - Oh he's okay.
-进来  -你好
- Come on in. - How are you doing?
-皮特  你好吗  -很好
- Hey Pete, how are ya? - Good.
-很高兴见到你们  -我也是
- Good to see ya. - Good. Good seeing you.
见过我老婆詹妮弗吗
You ever meet my wife Jennifer?
-没  跟高兴见到你  -你好
- No, hi. It's a real pleasure to meet you. - Hi. Hello.
-你好  -你好
- How are you? - Hey, how are you?
认识道克吗
You know Doc?
从没见过  艾弗里・克罗斯  你好
We've never meet. Avery Cross. How you doing?
-这是我老婆詹妮弗  你好
- That's my wife Jennifer. - Hey, how are you?
你们饿吗
You guys hungry?
不用  我们就走  你们享用吧
Nah we'll... we'll... we'll just.. we'll just leave you to it.
不  进来吧  吃点饭
No, come on in. Have some dinner.
不用  不不不  我们不是来吃饭的
Nah. No, no, no, we didn't come here for dinner.
-我们有好多吃的  快进来  -我
- Well we've got plenty of food. Come on in. - Well, I...
-给  -好
- There you go. - Oh yeah.
-来点沙拉吗  -很高兴我们一起吃饭
- Want some salad? - I'm glad we decided to do this.
很好  很高兴你们来
Oh good. I'm glad you guys came to visit.
谢谢
Thanks.
英雄回家了感觉如何
So how's it feel to have the hero home?
大概迫不及待想他赶快回去上班了吧
Probably can't wait for him to get back to work huh?
不  他回家很好
No. It's... it's great having him home, I just...
还好他没事
Thank God he's okay, you know.
上帝保佑  我们该干一杯
God bless that. I think we should toast on that.
-敬英雄  -敬英雄
- To our hero. - To hero boy.
-英雄  -来吧
- Hero boy. - Here you go.
很高兴你没事
Glad you're okay.
我进警队22年了
I've been on the force for twenty two years,
大概开过三四回枪
pulled the trigger maybe three, four times.
你加入半年就干掉了一个
You're on for six months, you already got one in the bag.
还是个白人
And he was white.
再加五十分
That's an extra fifty.
-他比我强吧  -没错
- Better him than me right? - You got that right.
你们晚上有事吗
You guys have any plans for tonight?
没事  只是...
No, we're just um...
-就这样吧  -是吗
- This is it. - Yeah?
今晚的计划就是跟你们大伙儿吃晚餐
This is the big plan. Having you guys here for dinner.
介意我们饭后
Would you mind if we stole
把英雄偷去干点活吗
the hero for a little police work, after this?
-今晚吗  -宵禁前就让他回家
- Tonight? - And we'll have him back by curfew.
我不知道  亲爱的
I don't know honey. You should
你今晚该休息  不然明晚吧
probably rest tonight. Maybe tomorrow night.
嗯  我们今晚有点需要他
Yeah... we kind of need him tonight.
-有问题吗  -你的腿怎么办呢
- Is there a problem? - What about your... your leg?
我们又不跑  我们可以抬他
Well, we're not going to be running. We'll carry him.
你们要干什么
What are you gonna do?
我们只想把他介绍给
We just want to introduce him to a
一群仰慕他的人
bunch of people who really admire him for what he did.
他们只想当面恭喜他
They just want to congratulate him in person.
好  听起来不错
Good, it sounds good.
我们过20分钟就走吧
We leave in about twenty minutes.
不是想吃完就跑  我们还得执勤
Not that we want to eat and run but, we are on duty.
没事  你们该去  那主意不错
No you should go. That's a great idea.
大家肯定很想见你
I'm sure everybody would love to meet you.
-好了  -你是英雄
- There you have it. - You're a hero.
你的声音有点讽刺的意味
I hear a little sarcasm in your voice.
-我吗  -对
- Me? - Yeah.
-他是英雄  -对
- He is a hero. - Yeah.
他当然是这里的英雄
He's a hero around here, that's for sure.
那你不介意我们带他走吧
You don't mind if we take him then, do you?
-不介意  这主意不错  -好的
- Not at all. I think it's a great idea. - Yeah. Alright.
好了  你被释放了
There you have it. You're released.
-放虎归山  -太好了
- Release the hounds. - Yeah.
艾弗里
Hey, Avery...
起码有时晚上她会愿意不那么男人吧
Does she sometimes like to tuck her balls up at least at night?
皮特  皮特
Hey, Pete. Pete.
-怎么了  -开下后备箱行吗
- What? - Can you pop the trunk?
好的  你老婆同意吗
Sure it's okay with her?
斯科特  你知道我执不了勤吧
Scott, you know I'm not on active duty right?
知道
Yeah, we're aware.
是打算给你点礼物
It's a little gift I got going for you.
走吧
Let's go.
警察
Police.
麻烦找罗米娜・古铁雷斯
Hi. Romina Gutierrez please.
-罗米娜在那  -嗯
- That's Romina right there. - Yeah.
我是德卢卡警官
Hi. I'm Officer Deluca.
-你是罗米娜・古铁雷斯吗  -对
- Romina Gutierrez?  - Yeah.
我们来搜查您的房子
Yeah, we're here to search your house.
搜什么
What for?
-证据  -什么证据
- For evidence. - Evidence for what?
我们在找卢克・格兰顿
We're looking for the money
或许有给你的钱
that Luke Glanton may or may have not given to you.
我们没有那种东西
Yeah, we don't have anything thing that that...
你不能就这么闯进来
Ah you can't just walk in here.
我可以
Yeah, I can.
-不行  -为什么
- No, you can't. - Why's that?
因为这是我家
Cause it's my house.
听着
Look...
你假装我们有搜查令
You assume that I have a warrant
我就假装你妈妈有居住证  好吗
and I'll assume that your mother has papers okay?
不会很久的
This won't take long.
来吧
Come on.
科菲
Kofi.
我们从楼上开始好吗
Can we just start upstairs okay?
不不不  我孩子在楼上
No, no, no, no. No, no, my baby is upstairs.
-我孩子在楼上睡觉  -孩子在楼上吗
- My baby, my baby is upstairs sleeping. - Baby's upstairs?
孩子正在楼上睡觉
Yeah, my baby is upstairs sleeping,
别从楼上开始
so we're not going to start...
没关系  我们不会吵醒孩子的
Alright. Well we won't rustle your baby.
别  别上去
No, no, no. Don't go up there.
-罗米娜  -放松  放松
- Romina... - Hey, hey, hey. Relax, relax.
-他不能上去  -他能
- He can't go up there. - Yeah, he can.
你要是愿意的话也可以上去
You can go up there if you want,
那就算人赃俱获了
but if we find evidence while you're up there,
你就要被逮捕了
your under arrest.
为什么
Why?
我们做了很多次了  会很安静的
We've done this a lot of times okay. It'll be quiet.
去吧  斯科特  安静点
Go on, Scotty. Be quiet.
-给我来杯咖啡吧  -好的  好的
- How about a cup of coffee? - Yes, yes, yes.
太好了
That'll be great.
我能进客厅吗
Is that fine? Go into your living room here?
是的  请进吧
Yeah, yeah. Go ahead.
谢谢
Thanks.
节哀顺变
Sorry for your loss.
罗米娜  我们走  走吧
Romina, lets go. Come on.
我们要做什么  到底要做什么
What are we doing? What are we doing here?
这太离谱了
Hey, this is crazy.
在外面等着
Wait outside.
我不等  我要走了  真他妈荒唐
I don't want to. We gotta go. This is fucked up.
-我们他妈的干嘛来这  -放开我
- Why the fuck are we here? - Let go of my arm man.
-我们到底要做什么  -放开我
- What the fuck are we doing here? - Let go of my arm.
斯科特  我们他妈的来做什么
Scott, what the fuck are we doing here?
闭嘴
Shut up.
-你认识卢克多久了  -有几年了
- About how long did you know Luke? - A couple of years.
-你知道他抢银行了吗  -不知道
- Did you know he was robbing banks? - No.
-完全不知道  -是的
- You didn't know that at all? - No.
因为工作需要
Let me just ask you one more
我再问你一遍
time because this is... this is what we do.
-你对这笔钱一无所知  -是的
- You have no knowledge to this money? - No.
-警官  我对天发誓  -钱不在这吗
- Officer I swear to God. - It's not here?
-不在  -也没在外面
- No - It's not outside?
如果我要藏什么东西
If I was gonna hid something
我肯定藏在心腹之地
I would hide it closest to my heart.
斯科特
Scott.
抱起他来
Pick him up.
-把孩子抱起来  -我们不该这样
- Pick up the baby. - I don't think we should.
我不想弄醒他
I don't want to wake him.
-我不想抱他  -抱起来  抱起来
- I don't wanna pick him up. - Pick him up, pick him up.
好了
I'm good.
放回去  我们走
Put him back. Let's go.
-怎么样  -他们清白了
- What's up? - Yeah, they're clean.
好的  那就不打扰了
Alrighty, let's get out of your hair.
是你找到的  斯科特  拜托
You got this Scotty, c'mon.
快帮帮他  行吗
Help him out, will you.
-斯科特  停  停  -让我数数
- Scotty stop, stop. - Give me a chance to count it.
按你这么数
You... you going to count like that,
我们凌晨五点都数不完
we're going to be here till five in the morning.
那你怎么数
How are you gonna count it?
-你有点钞机啊  -是啊  是啊
- You got a money counter there asshole? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-一万四大洋  -一万四吗
- Fourteen grand. - $14,000?
我们就不用平分了
Well it's not going to be a even split
大份当然属于我们的英雄
because the lion's share is going to our hero.
就当做是非官方的危险补贴吧
Consider it unofficial hazard pay.
我们送你的
From us to you.
笑纳吧
Enjoy it.
我们部门是不会给你补贴的
Cause you're not going to get it from the department.
别都花在同一个地方
Don't spend it all on one place.
这他妈是你应得的  别忘了
You fucking earned that. Don't forget that.
不错吧  一晚收获颇丰
Not bad huh? Not bad for a nights work.
我们齐聚一堂
We're gathered here to
来赞美一个让我们引以为豪的警察
celebrate a cop who makes other cops proud.
看到他渐渐康复
We can all rest a little easier tonight
我们可以松一口气
now that he is on the path to recovery.
女士们先生们  艾弗里・克罗斯警官
Ladies and gentleman, Officer Avery Cross.
谢谢你们的支持
Thank you. Thank you for your support.
读法学院的时候  我们常常谈论正义
When I was in law school, we used to always talk about Justice.
我们讨论正义
We had discussions about justice.
但也仅仅如此而已
That's just what they were.
仅限于讨论
Discussions.
我之所以成为一名警察
I joined the police force
是因为我想和最勇敢的人一起
because I wanted to work alonside the
并肩作战
brave men and women who
我们都知道光说解决不了问题
know some problems can't be solved by talk.
但谁都不想遭遇
But no one wants to be in the situation
我几周前的情况
I found myself in a couple of weeks ago.
我诚然希望有不一样的结果
I certainly wish it had turned out differently.
说实话  有时候我希望
I'm not going to lie. Sometimes I haven't wished that
那天闯进房子的不是我
maybe it wasn't me that was called upon that house that day.
但这就是我的工作
But that's the job.
我无法设想自己从事其他的工作
But I can't think of another line of work I would rather be in.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么样
How does it feel?
我觉得没什么帮助
I'm not sure it's doing much good.
-聚光灯下的生活呢  -我都想结束了
- How's the spotlight? - I'm ready for it to end.
别担心  会结束的
Don't worry. It will.
警局总是这样
You know the police always put on a big show
把这种事小题大做
when something like this happens
因为他们只剩英雄牌可打了
because the hero card is the only one they have to play.
我倒是没想那么多
I'm not really thinking about that Dad.
我只是想回去工作
I'm just trying to get back to work.
如果你已经计划好
You know if you planned this
就再好不过了
it couldn't have turned out any better.
但这样在警局
You're not going to make it work
是行不通的
for you in the police department.
我保证
I promise you that.
我不是来这上课的爸爸
I didn't come here to be lectured Dad.
你骗我  你说游泳对膝盖好
You tricked me. You said the pool would be good for my knee.
-抱歉  -我不像你那样会算计
- Sorry. - You know, I'm not as calculated as you are.
我的生活不是一场竞选  简单得多
My life is not a campaign. It's much simpler.
是啊
Yeah.
对一个不是参加竞选的人来说
Though for somebody who's not campaigning,
你昨天可是来了一次精彩演说
you gave a hell of a speech yesterday.
我肯定投票给你
You certainly have my vote.
再加上膝盖这个小金矿
Plus that knee is a gold mine.
真的  瘸腿在政治中不少见
No I mean it. A limp goes a long way in politics.
罗斯福  美国前总统  因患有脊髓灰质炎症而导致腿部残疾
想想罗斯福
Look at Roosevelt.
我得去找警长  我得去找警长
I got to go see the chief. I got to go see the chief.
-去哪啊  老兄  -不知道
- Where you going, brother? - I don't know. I don't know.
坏消息吗  会是坏消息吗
Is it bad news? Is it gonna be bad news?
天啊
Oh, Jesus Christ.
别乱了发型  靓仔
Don't mess your hair up, pretty boy.
我今天接到地方检察官金库伦的电话
I got a call today from D.A. Killcullen.
关上门
Close the door.
内部调查结果
The state internal investigation
将对卢克・格兰顿射击视为合法
into shooting of Luke Glanton has been deemed lawful.
恭喜你  警官
Congratulations officer.
这事可以放下了  恢复工作吧
You can put it behind you. Get back to police work.
问题是你可以尽快回去巡逻吗
The question is can you go back out on patrol anytime soon?
如果可以的话  还能保证效率吗
And if you could, can you be effective?
我觉得不能
I don't think that I can.
没关系
That's okay. You know what
这还有很多工作可以做呢
there's a lot of jobs to be done around here.
你也知道的
That in ways and you know that.
很多工作
In ways that are much more important
都比外勤更重要
than what happens out on the street.
很高兴您这么说
I'm so glad that you said that.
警长  我想了很久
Because Chief I've thought a lot about this and the...
我觉得  我最好是
I... I think I can be best utilized as
去特殊调查组做主管
as lieutenant in... in charge of special investigations.
那个部门正好在重组
There's a lot of restructuring
我实际上
within the division that I've actually formally...
我不能这么做
I can't fucking do that.
当然  您当然能  我意思是
Well yeah, of course... of course you could. I mean...
克罗斯  得了吧
Cross, come on.
你受过这么良好的教育  去那也太傻了
You paid too much for your education to act so stupid.
正是因为我受过这样的教育
But I think it is the very fact
所以我才去思考
that I do have a education like this that perhaps...
如何重组这个部门
the reason why I thought
才能使这个部门
about how restructuring the... the unit...
对大家更有益
Um, the division can actually benefit you, me, and a couple...
克罗斯  我欣赏你的雄心壮志  真的
Cross, I appreciate you ambition. I really do.
我觉得
Uh and uh I think... you know...you..
我觉得你能成一名好警察
I think you are going to be a great cop.
你已经是名好警察了  你是个英雄
You are a great cop. You're a hero.
但这件事  你得面对现实
But at this point. Right now. You gotta get back to real life.
-现实就是你有两种选择  -什么选择
- And in real life you got two choices. - Which are?
-你可以因伤退休  -我不想退休
- You can retire on disability. - I don't want to do that.
很好  我也不想让你退休
Alright, good. I don't want you to do that either. Or...
或者以你现有的级别指派
You can be reassigned at your current rank.
就是这样
That's it.
你得一步步升上来
You gotta work your way up, man.
伙计  听说你在这
Hey man. I heard you were down here.
你好
Hey.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你怎么穿了便衣
What are you doing on plain clothes?
你没听说吗  我调到缉捕队了
Oh you didn't hear? I made Vice.
-滚开  -真的
- Get the fuck outta here. - Yeah man,
我和德卢卡搭档
I'm actually paired up with Deluca.
好吧  你拿的什么
Good. What have you got for me?
几个小杂种
Oh yeah. A couple of mutts left this
把毒品落在后座了
in the back seat of their car with a leaky substance.
好吧
Oh nice.
什么时候我们一起聚聚  吃点东西
So when are we going to get together? Grab a little bite.
我想好好谈谈
I want to talk about some things.
-可以啊  -好的
- Sounds great. - Alright man.
-联系我  -好的
- Page me. - Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
我求你这事儿挺敏感的
What I'm about to ask you is very sensitive.
因为把你当朋友才求你
The only reason I'm asking you is because you're my friend.
我不知道怎么帮你
Well I don't know what I can do to help...
-你说吧  -好的
- but yeah. What do you need? - Alright. Right on.
德卢卡和我在忙这个案子
Deluca and I have been working on this case right.
我要你保密
And uh... I'm going to need you to keep this to yourself.
这有点涉及隐私
It's a little private.
我不想让任何人知道  好吗
And uh... I don't want anybody to know about it, okay?
好的
Okay.
德卢卡和我的这个案子里有个婊子
Deluca and I have been working with this fucking hooker.
我们得想办法摆平她
We gotta fucking head her off with some coke.
德卢卡和我想
So Deluca and I thought that you know, if...
我们需要在证据室有个临时接应
We need some temporary access to the evidence room.
我们需要你搞点手脚
We need you to get some shit.
我们得摆平这个贱人  他是这么想的
We gotta hit this bitch off. That's what he need.
你那七千块的事我努力帮你打点好了
I really tried to look out for you with that seven grand.
现在你也得帮我们
Now I need you to look out for me.
我是认真的  老兄  得有来有往
I'm serious, bro. This is how it works.
别担心  没事的
Hey, don't worry. It's okay.
我没想吓到你
So I didn't mean to startle you.
没事  我只是想给你点东西
It's okay. I just want to give you something.
听着
Alright. Listen.
这是我们从你房子里搜到的钱
This is the money we recovered from your house okay.
你拿着它
I want you to have it.
我不知道这是什么
I don't know what that is.
你不用再见到我  拿着钱
You don't have to ever see me again. Just take the money.
别把我当警察  就当我是个普通人
I'm not here as a police officer. I'm here as a regular guy.
听着  听着  听我说
Listen, listen, listen.
-滚开  -听我说
- Get the fuck away. - Listen to me. Listen.
你毁了我儿子的生活
You fucked up my son's life.
也就是毁了我的生活  滚开
Therefore you fucked up my life. Get the fuck away from me.
我该早点拿给你的  抱歉
I should have brought this to you sooner. I apologize.
这是上次搜查的时候
This was recovered from
搜到的钱
a house during a search.
什么  等等
No, what, what, wait a minute.
这只是搜到的一小部分
That's just a small fraction of what's going on.
等等  克罗斯
Wait a minute, Cross.
什么也别说了
Don't say another word.
-什么意思  -不  不  别说话
- What do you mean? - No, no, no. Don't say another word.
你指望我能做点什么
What do you expect me to do with this?
-你开玩笑的吧  -胡扯
- You're joking right? - This is shit.
警长
Chief.
这不是我的问题
This ain't my problem. Alright.
这是你的问题
This is your problem.
这他妈的是我们部门的问题
This is our problem of the fucking police department
我把这个给你
and I'm bringing it to your attention
因为这他妈的才是我应该做的
because that's what I should fucking do!
是吗  你这么想
Oh yeah? Is that right?
-没错  -这是你应该做的
- Yeah! - Is that what you should do?
-他妈的出卖兄弟  -警长
- Rat out other fucking cops? - Chief
真他妈不能相信
This is unfucking believable alright.
带着钱滚出去
Get this shit outta here.
见鬼
Fuck.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
回家
Going home.
你知道那件事
You know that thing...
你和斯科特谈的那件事吗
you and Scotty been talking about?
知道
Yeah.
当然知道
Sure.
那我们得好好谈谈了
Well you and I have to talk about it.
跟我走
Follow me.
老爸
Hey, Pop.
艾弗里
Avery.
我有一个办法
There's a way out of this.
你肯定不会喜欢的
You're not going to like it.
想听吗
You want to hear?
想  我想听
Yeah, I wanna hear it.
你得从你们警区下手
We'll start with the precinct.
还有人信任你吗
Anybody there still trust you?
斯科特
Scott.
那就从斯科特开始
We'll start with Scott.
看那游击手
Playing shortstop.
看起来不错  更强壮了
Looks good. Looks bigger. Jesus Christ.
你当时真是吓了卢克一跳啊
You really gave Luke a quiet scare.
他准备摆脱你了  摆脱整件事
He's ready to dump you. The whole thing.
我他妈的受够了这些考验了
Enough with these fucking tests alright.
要么就有事说事  要么就别烦我
Either ask me to help you or just leave me the fuck alone.
我要你进到证据室
I need you to go into the locker.
把麦金伦的箱子拿出来
I need you to take the McKillen case out.
那有一公斤重  是个大箱子
It's a... it's a kilo. It's a big brick.
上面写着麦金伦  记住了吗
It says Mckillen across it okay?
我要你拿出一大块  放在包里
I need you take break up a chunk. I need you to put it in a bag.
我会去找你  明天早上把它拿走
I'm going to come by. I'm going to pick it up tomorrow morning.
如果有人问你  这个怎么变轻了
If somebody asks you "Hey why is this lighter?".
就说  我是新手啊
Say "Hey, you know what, I'm a rookie".
难免出错
"I made a mistake."
你他妈清清白白的还拿过荣誉奖章
You're a squicky clean fucking lawyer with a Medal of Honor.
没人会多问的
Nobody's going to question you, okay.
你得帮我  我也是身不由己
You gotta do this for me. I'm in a jam with these guys.
没问题
No problem.
好  我就知道可以指望你
Alright. I know I can count on you.
当然
Yeah.
告诉迈克我爱他  我得走了
Tell Mike I love him. I gotta go.
我要你进到证据室
I need you to go into the locker.
把麦金伦的箱子拿出来
I need you to take the McKillen case out.
那有一公斤重  是个大箱子
It's a kilo. It's a big brick.
上面写着麦金伦  记住了吗
It says Mckillen across it okay?
我要你拿出一大块  放在包里
I need you take break up a chunk. I need you to put it in a bag.
我会去找你  明天早上把它拿走
I'm going to come by. I'm going to pick it up tomorrow morning.
好吗
Alright?
如果有人问你  这个怎么变轻了
If somebody asks you "Hey why is this lighter?".
就说  我是新手啊
Say "Hey, you know what, I'm a rookie".
难免出错
"I made a mistake."
你他妈清清白白的还拿过荣誉奖章
You're a squicky clean fucking lawyer with a Medal of Honor.
没人会多问的
Nobody's going to question you, okay.
你得帮我  我也是身不由己
You gotta do this for me. I'm in a jam with these guys.
没问题
No problem.
给内部调查科听过了吗
Shown this to I.A.?
当然没
Of course not.
给你听听更方便点
Handing it to you on a silver platter.
知道这意味着什么吗
Got any idea what this means?
真要这样做
Are you ready do it?
真的吗  真要这样做
Are you son? Are you really ready?
他们会搞死你的
Cause they're going to fucking tear you in half.
我要你保证
I'm going to need you're assurance
案子要一直跟进下去
that you're gonna follow through.
真的吗
Really?
而且我需要完全的豁免权
And I'm going to want full immunity when you do.
你不能就这样
You can't just walk in here
命令我该如何做  知道吗
and tell me what the fuck to do. You understand?
同时
And when you do,
我要当助理检察官
I want to be made assistant district attorney.
我有法学学位并通过了律师资格考试
I have a law degree and I passed the bar.
-现在没这样的职位空缺  -那弄一个
- I don't have a spot for you right now. - Make a spot.
我不会那样做
I won't do that.
我不能打个响指就让你去当助理检察官
I can't just snap my fingers and make you assistant D.A.
你可以拒绝
You can say no.
你当然可以拒绝  那么我就会走出这门
You can say no. I'll walk out this door.
走到报社  抖出我所知的一切
I walk over to the Gazette. I'll tell them everything I know.
包括这次谈话
Including this conversation.
别  听着  你哪都别去
You're not, listen. You're not going anywhere.
别  听着
Don't. Listen.
把它放回桌面  我他妈答应你
Put it back on the table, I'll fucking do it.
-三样都能做到吗  -是的
- All three things? - Alright.
我不能保证你能在那待多久
I'm not going to promise you how long you're going to stay there.
别想跟我握手
You're not going to shake my fucking hand pal.
我会帮你当上助理检察官
I'll make you assistant D.A.
但我是不会跟你握手的
I'm never going to shake your fucking hand.
你真是机关算尽
You're too smart for your own good.
到那找个好角度拍
Get right in there for a good shot.
警探  对于这些指控你有何回应
Detective, how do you respond to these allegations?
毒品  贪污  帮派
Drugs, corruption, and gangs.
这并非斯克奈塔第警方所作的调查
It's not an investigation by the Schenectady Police Department.
而是来自斯克奈塔第警方内部的调查
It's an investigation into the Schenectady Police Department.
今日稍早  地方检察官金库伦宣布
Earlier today, D.A. Killcullen announced
他所在部门将会联同联邦调查局
that his office, along with the FBI,
提起诉讼  而这班来自
will be handing down indictments that
斯克奈塔第的警官
would lead to the arrest
将会被依法逮捕
of these Schenectady police officers.
地方检察官于今日作出检控
The D.A. is making allegations today
警察缉捕队的职责本应是捉拿黑帮
that the Vice officers were acting like the gangs
但他们自身却干着黑帮的勾当
that they were suppose to be hunting.
德卢卡警官涉嫌窃取毒品和钱财
Officer Deluca stole drugs and money,
还有物证室的枪械
even guns from inside the evidence room here.
据称警察会将这些偷来的物证转给罪犯
Officials say that with that stolen evidence,
使其提高实力  制造大案
the cops paid criminals to help set up their rivals.
再一举歼灭  尽显警威
Which then led to those headline robbing arrests.
地方检察官今日也宣布了此案的关键证人
The D.A. Announced a star witness in the case today.
他便是警界之光  艾弗里・克罗斯
Hero cop, Avery Cross,
在不到1年前  他在执勤过程中
who less than a year ago was shot in the line of duty
为解救两位居民
while trying to save two Schenectady residents
不幸被摩托大盗给射伤
from the alledged Moto Bandit.
杰西卡・莱顿来自斯克奈塔第的报道
In Schenectady, I'm Jessica Layton,
-13新闻频道  -没事的
- News Channel 13. - It's going to be alright.
谢谢杰西  此案是本地区有史以来
Thanks Jess. It's the largest case
最大的诈骗案
of fraud this region has seen.
15 年 后
当我还是个孩子时
You know when I was a kid,
看到穿着法官袍的父亲
I used to look at my Dad dressed in judge's robes
觉得他就跟超人一样
and I used to think that my father was a superhero.
这么说一点都不为过
And I don't think I was far off.
他具备法官的高尚品质
He had that quality that
有着无限的怜悯之心
judges have where they have tremendous compassion.
但同时也铁面无私
But they are also ferocious at the same time.
不畏强权
He wasn't afraid of making enemies.
也因此结交了许多朋友
I think that's probably why he had so many friends.
在他昏迷之际  我告诉他
I had the chance right before he fell into the coma to tell him that
我将为他去竞选司法部长
I was dedicating my run for Attorney General to him.
他摇摇头  我不解其意
And he shook his head no and I didn't understand why.
我凑上前  只听见他轻声对我说
So I leaned in close that he can whisper and he said to me,
竞选只是过程  赢才是目的
"I'll take the win, not the run."
这就是我的父亲  这就是阿尔
That was my dad. That was Al.
-儿子  要跟我一块走吗  -好
- Son, you want to come with me? - Sure.
-艾弗里  -怎么了
- Avery. - Yeah.
-能给你谈几句吗  -当然
- Can I talk to you for a minute? - Sure.
把车门关上
Close the door.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我们得谈谈AJ
We have to talk about AJ.
他想跟你住一块
He wants to come and live with you.
为这事他一直没完没了
He won't stop asking me about it.
真的吗
Really?
这也不失为一个好建议
I guess that's a good idea at some point.
我觉得他需要你
I think he needs you.
他不跟你住一块的话
I think if he doesn't come and live with you,
就真要误入歧途了
he's going to completely go off the rails.
不过现在  你也知道
It's just that right now, you know,
我在忙竞选  还有其他事
with the campaign and everything,
真不是个好时机
it's just not an ideal time.
我的意思是  我要怎么跟他相处
I mean, what am I going to do with him?
我又不知道他喜好
I don't know what he likes or...
这对他或是任何人都没好处
I just don't think it will be good for him or anybody.
-对吧  -知道了
- I mean, come on. - Okay.
-你知道的  -那你去跟他说
- You know that. - Well you can tell him that.
-詹妮弗  -我要跟他怎么说
- Jennifer. - What am I suppose to tell him?
我只是不想...
I just don't...
干嘛非得挑这时候
Why, why, why are you doing this right now?
你可以现在就跟他说
You can tell him now.
明天一早我们就前往水牛城
Tomorrow we're going to head to Buffalo in the morning.
周三到纽约市市郊
Wednesday outer boroughs in New York City.
晚上会跟艾尔・史密斯吃晚餐
Then the Al Smith dinner at night.
够时间吗
Do we have time to get there?
绝对够  最后的行程是在皇后区附近
We do, absolutely. We'll get... We'll have our last event,
我们会到上西区
close in Queens. We'll hit the Upper West Side.
之后入住华尔道夫饭店
Then we have to be at the Waldolf.
请那个叫约瑟的曼哈顿司机如何
How about Youseth that driver we have from Manhattan?
-可以  -皇后区的行程如何
- We can use Youseth totally. - What's going on in Queeens?
在皇后区要参加一个关于环境议题的活动
In Queens, he's going to do an event on environmental issues.
就是讲一些环保措施  比如噪音防护
Talking about some of the, protecting the... the Sound,
诸如此类的环境议题
and doing some of the environmental stuff.
周四到罗契斯特市吃午餐
And Thursday at the Rochester for lunch,
到那要点一个叫
you're going to go to a place
杂烩拼盘的特色菜
where you are going to order something called the Garbage Plate.
你安排好就行
I just want you to be prepared for it.
-这你看过没  -还没
- Did you see that? - Yeah, no, I just...
-周日早上参加黑人教会  -太棒了
- Then Sunday morning black churches. - Oh perfect.
好的  我们可以...
Alright. I think we can get...
你爸爸是艾弗里・克罗斯
Avery Cross?
是的  我叫AJ
Yeah. AJ
AJ
AJ?
-是的  -你好  AJ
- Yeah. - Hi, AJ.
你是从哪所高中来的
So what high school are you coming from?
特洛伊高中
From Troy High School.
你是特洛伊来的  -是的
- You're coming from Troy? - Yeah.
也不是很远  为什么来斯克奈塔第
Okay, so not too far away. What brings you to Schenectady?
是我爸让我来的
Um, my dad wanted me here.
你爸让你来的
You're dad wanted you here?
是的  高三了  想让我换换环境
Yeah, for my senior year he wanted me to move.
你什么想法
What about you?
想高三的时候到这里来吗
Did you want to come here for you're senior year?
不知道  可能...不太想
I don't know. Yeah, I guess not. Not really.
在学校有认识的人吗
Do you know anybody here at the high school?
没有吗
No, don't know anybody?
转过头去
Just peak over you're shoulder.
他妈的转过头去
Peak over you're fucking shoulder.
看到没  你好  你好
There you go. Hello there, hello.
你好
Hello.
你不喜欢她们吗
You don't like them girls?
也许你看腻了吧
I don't know. Maybe you're just used to it.
在我那可没这么正点的妞  你懂的
They ain't got girls like that where I come from. You feel me.
你是从哪里来的
Where are you from?
特洛伊
Troy.
特洛伊吗
Troy?
-是的  知道特洛伊吗  -听说过
- Yeah. You heard of Troy? - Yeah, I've heard of Troy.
-特洛伊在哪  -老兄  它就在隔壁
- Where's Troy at? - It's fucking right next door, dude.
就在隔壁
Right next door?
我猜你是长岛来的
I would have guessed you were from Long Island.
怎么说
Why's that?
那里的人说话就像你一样
It's where people that talk like you come from.
知道吗
Ah ha ha, see.
老兄  在这我都无聊透了
I'm bored as a motherfuck around here dude.
我他妈在这待了三天
I've been here for like fucking three days.
无聊得快要疯掉
I'm bored out of my fucking mind.
上学也就这样
Well school can do that to you.
你们平常有什么消遣  没有吗
Well what you dudes do for fun? Nothing?
就这样  一年都这样无聊地度过吗
This is it? This is what I got? For a year?
-不  我们有消遣  -是什么
- No, we got somethings. - What?
别跟我说是逛商场  要真是的话
Don't say like a mall. If you say a fucking mall...
我对天发誓
I swear to God.
那你有什么消遣
What do you do?
我嗑药
I get high.
那倒可以有
Well we can do some of that around here.
你也抽烟  我看见过
I can tell you smoke. I've seen you from back there.
像个不合群的瘾君子
You're one of them loner stoners is what I call them. Right?
你也爱嗑药
You like to get high and
磕嗨了就爱待在房里发泄
like chill in your room and draw and shit.
接下来要干嘛呢
Whatcha trying to do with the rest of this day then?
要去上数学课吗
You trying to go to math class?
不想爽一下吗
You don't want to go get high?
-走吧  -走
- Lets go. - Alright, lets go.
七宝奇谋  经典儿童冒险电影  全片有相当热闹的机关布景
知道我想到什么了吗  《七宝奇谋》
You know what this reminds me of? The Goonies.
知道这电影不  这就像他们那洞穴
You know that movie? Where like they're all in a cave.
想抽烟  就向我要
You want a cigarette, just ask homie.
我得抽根烟
I'll take a cigarette.
我爽翻天时喜欢来根烟
I like smoking cigarettes when I'm high.
你爽到冒烟时喜欢抽烟
You like smoking when your smoking?
来根薄荷香烟吗  像呼吸新鲜空气一样
You smoke menthols man? Like a breath of fresh air.
就像呼吸到新鲜空气一样毫不在乎
Like a breath of fresh air which you don't care.
我保证你也能把烟喷得到处都是
You got the smoke puff glowing everywhere. I swear.
一起来
Yo, here we go.
口水是我子弹  嘴巴是我枪杆
I say my spit is my ammo. My mouth is my gun.
我动动舌头
And I shoot up your whole squadron
就能把你整个舰队干掉
with one flip of my tongue and you're done.
这你写的
When did you write that?
不骗你  是我写的
Nah I'm not trying to lie. I wrote that.
这里真他妈安静
Fucking quiet around here.
当我还是个孩子的时候
Shit though, when I was a kid,
这里可多孩子玩耍了
there was always kid playing here, you know.
你小时候到过这
Oh you came here when you was a kid?
是的  偶尔会跟父母来
Yeah man. I come here with my parents sometimes.
-你父母还在一起吗  -是的
- Your parents still together? - Yeah.
那很好啊
That's cool.
-他们还在一起  -是啊  还好吧
- That they're still together. - Yeah, it's alright.
尽管那不是我的生父
It's not my real dad, though.
你的生父呢
Where's your real dad at?
死了  好像是车祸
He died actually. Like in a car accident or something.
靠
Shit.
现在抽的也不过是点大麻
Hey this is kinda bud dude.
你知道在哪可以搞到摇头丸吗
But umm, do you know where I can score some X?
知道
Yeah.
今晚来点
For tonight?
刚刚顶多算前戏  高潮在后头呢
Well we just did a downer. We gotta get up.
记住下次自己一个人来
Remember to come back by yourself alright?
好的  没问题
Yeah man, you got it.
走吧
Let's go.
-让我看看  -什么
- Let me see it. - What?
-让我验验货  -你没开玩笑吧
- Let me see the fucking drugs. - You fucking seriously man?
快让我看看我的小药丸
Let me see my fucking drugs.
这他妈的什么玩意
What the fuck?
我给了你500美元
I gave you five hundo.
是啊  买了20粒药丸
Yeah, that's twenty pills.
是通货膨胀还是怎样
Yo that's inflation or something right?
他妈的  该死  有条子
Oh yo, what the fuck son. Dead ass, it's the fucking five-o.
-该死的  -该死的
- Oh fuck! - Fuck!
-警察  把手举起  -警察  趴下
- Police! Let me see your hands! - Police! Get on the ground!
- 趴下  趴到地上  -知道了
- Down, on the ground! - Fuck you alright!
-趴下  -手指交叉
- Get on the ground! - Interlace your fingers.
他从几个孩子身上搜出了摇头丸
He scored Ecstasy from some Schenectady kid.
谁逮捕他们的
Who arrested them?
两个巡警  麦克肯跟波特
A couple of beat cops. McCracken and Potter.
-你认识他们  -我能让他们息事宁人
- You know these guys? - They'll sit on it if I ask them to.
还有其他人看见吗
Did anybody else see anything in there?
没有  这我敢保证
No, I made sure of that.
-知道他们俩是什么关系吗  -朋友
- Didn't you get any sense that the knew this kid or? - Friends.
-就只是他们两个  -是的
- Just the two of them? - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
另一个孩子叫什么
What's this other kid's name?
詹森・康肯
Jason Kancam.
前些年入店行窃也被我抓到过
I busted him a few years ago for some shoplifting.
他叫什么
What's his name?
詹森・康肯
Jason Kancam.
-戈登  把监听器先关掉  -好的
- Gordon, can we kill the mic on three. - Yeah.
爸爸  我闯祸了  我知道...
Dad. I fucked up, I know and...
我知道现在你没时间
And I know you don't have time
处理这些破事儿
to deal with this stuff right now.
别搞他  好吗
Not him. Okay?
-什么  -我让你离他远点
- What? - I want you to leave him alone.
知道吗
Alright?
-懂了吗  -为什么
- Okay? - Why?
别他妈嬉皮笑脸的  听见没
Wipe that fucking smirk off your face! You hear me!
我让你别去搞那孩子  听见没
I want you to leave that fucking kid alone, alright?
看着我  看着我
Look at me! Look at me!
你还想跟我住一块  是吧
You want to come live with me right?
你觉得这很好玩吗  在这时候
You think this is easy for me? During this time? Huh?
我尽量去迁就了  还不是为了你
I'm trying to make this work. I'm doing it for you.
你爱干嘛干嘛去
You can have anything you want.
但你别再去碰那孩子
But I don't want you to touch that kid.
离他远点  你他妈听清楚了吗
You leave him alone. You underfucking stand me?
-说知道了  -知道了
- Say yes! - Yes.
-看着我说  -知道了
- Look at me and say yes. - Yes.
-请报上姓名  -詹森・康肯
- Can you state your name for the record? - Jason Kancam.
-詹森  你多大了  -17岁
- Jason, how old are you? - Seventeen.
-你父母今天都在场吗  -是的
- Are your parents here today? - Yes. Yes.
请上来一下
Can you come up please?
-你们是詹森的父母  -是的
- You're Jason's parents? - Yes.
詹森  你被检控的罪名为
Jason, you've been charged with criminal possession
非法持有三级违禁品罪
of a controlled substance in the third degree.
法律顾问  你要放弃提审吗
Counselor, do you waive a formal reading of the charges?
是的  法官  根据我当事人的状况
Yes, please your Honor. In regards to my clients status
以及与地方检察官的商讨
there has been a discussion with the District Attorney.
这案子今天就能
Your Honor, I may be able to have
初步结案了  法官大人
this case tentatively resolved today.
我恳请二次传唤
So I ask if you could put it on for Second Call?
二次传唤
Second Call.
这是三级重罪
This is a C felony,
詹森可能面临5到15年刑期
so Jason could do anywhere between five and fifteen years.
可公诉人
But I'm getting the impression
则更倾向于
from the Prosecutor that they may be willing
将他定为轻罪
to reduce it today to a misdemeanor.
在本次案件当中
The offer on his particular case
他被关押的这一天将算作服刑
would be time served, which is the day he spent in jail.
并罚款
And a fine.
就是这样
And that would be it.
-他今天可以和我们回家吗  -可以
- Can he come home with us today? - He can.
今天你们的幸运日  有人帮你们摆平了
Guess it's your lucky day. Somebody is looking out for you.
那天晚上我不是有心拖累你
Look, I didn't mean to get you busted the other night, alright.
对不起
I'm sorry.
确实是个让人难忘的夜晚
Yeah, that was a pretty shitty fucking night.
别担心
But don't worry about it.
没过五分钟我就离开了
I was outta there in five fucking minutes still.
你以为我一整晚
You think I'm going to sit there
都在那破地方傻坐着吗
and get fucked up the ass all night?
你回家以后怎么样
What happened when you got home?
我上了楼
Went upstairs.
想要睡觉
Tried to go to sleep
可那阵兴奋劲还没有过去
but I was still tripping like a motherfucker.
怎么了  你回家以后呢
Why? What happened to you when you got home?
我很好  哥们
I'm cool, man.
你妈妈很担心你吗
Ah your moms was all worried and shit?
伙计  我妈妈...
Ah man, my moms...
我很好  哥们
I'm cool, man.
真的吗
Really?
我今天看见那个家伙了
Cause I saw that guy today.
哪个家伙
What guy?
你老爸
Your dad.
你老爸真他妈不错
Nice of your fucking dad.
他什么时候到你家的
When did he move in?
你他妈胡说什么呢  AJ
What the fuck are you talking about, AJ?
我只是好奇而已  别激动
I just wanna know. Don't freak out...
你他妈的有病吧
What the fuck is your problem?
-冷静  伙计  -你有病吧  AJ
- Chill, dude. Chill. - What's your problem, AJ?
逗逗你而已
Just fucking around.
别太认真
Be so serious.
你脾气可真不怎么样  老兄
You got a fucking temper, B.
如果你继续这副德行
You need to watch that shit.
一定会惹祸上身的
It's gonna get you in fucking trouble.
今天在学校怎么样  瓦妮萨
How's school, Vanessa?
还好  就是数学有点小问题
It's okay. I had trouble with math.
我爸爸究竟怎么了
Hey, what's the deal with my dad?
怎么了
What?
你真有那么恨他吗
What? Did you like really hate him or something?
他叫什么名字
What was his name?
-该死的  -他叫什么名字
- God damn it. - What was his first name?
我不会告诉你的
I'm not doing this.
妈妈为什么从不提起我爸爸
How come mom never talks to me about my dad?
我就是你爸爸
I'm your father.
你知道的  我没有骗你
Search your feelings. You know it to be true.
和不和你说是她自己的事
It's her business to talk about it, not talk about you.
外婆倒是时常提起
Grandma used to tell me something.
是吗  她都说些什么
Yeah? What she used to say?
她说...
She said like...
我爸是个罪犯
Just that he was like an outlaw.
你知道吧
You know.
听起来很酷吗
Sound cool to you?
我不知道
I don't know.
他不是你爸爸
He's not your father.
不是
Not really.
他是那个小宝宝的爸爸
Just some guy with a baby.
我才是你爸爸
I'm your father.
从你一出生起  我就在你身边
Been there since you were born.
我一直很爱你
I will always love you.
最起码告诉我他的名字  好吗
Can you at least tell me his name?
谷歌搜索  卢克・格兰顿
摩托大盗被警方击毙
被击毙
昨日被杀
射杀
有人吗
Hello?
怎么了
Yeah?
我找罗宾
I'm looking for Robin.
我就是罗宾  找我有什么事吗
Yeah. I'm Robin. What can I do for you?
我想和你谈谈有关卢克・格兰顿的事情
I was hoping to talk with you about Luke Glanton.
我是他儿子
I'm his son.
你是卢克・格兰顿的儿子?
Luke Glanton's son?
是的
Yeah.
好吧  进来喝杯啤酒吧
Well. Come on back, get a beer.
但愿还在这个箱子里
Bet he's down here in this box.
如果我没记错的话
If I remember rightly...
好了
Well...
没错
Yeah.
这个家伙就是你爸爸  这里
That guy is your dad. That's him there.
这是那头蠢猪  就是他逮住了你爸爸
And that's the pig there. The one that pegged him.
他怎么样了
What happened to him?
谁  那个警察吗
Who? The cop?
忘记他吧  别想了
Ah forget about him, man. Don't, don't start there.
我给你看点好东西  给你看点好东西
I'll show you good things. I'll show you good things.
来
Come on.
过去我和你爸爸聊天的时候
You are standing right where
他总是站在你现在站的这个位置
your dad used to stand when we used to talk.
你爸爸是个好人
He's a good guy. Your dad.
那副眼镜  我很久没见了
Yeah, those glasses. I haven't seen them in a long time.
这副眼镜是他的  真够傻的
Them, them. They're his. Those goofy glasses.
-这是他的吗  -是的
- These were his? - Yeah.
收下吧  他一定希望你收下这副眼镜
You keep those. He would have wanted you to have them.
他擅长什么呢
Was he good at anything?
他是我这辈子见过的
Yeah, he was the best motorcycle rider
最棒的摩托车手
I've ever seen in my life.
最棒的
Best.
-是吗  -他是最棒的
- Yeah? - Best.
无可匹敌  最好的车手
Never see another one like him. Best.
他就像
He was like...
没什么  就这样
Nothing. We're here.
你们是好朋友吗
You guys good friends?
我想是的
Yeah, I think we were.
你还留着他的车子吗
You still got his bike?
不  他的车不在了
No, his bike is gone.
被警察没收了
Police took it.
我觉得他们应该把它销毁了
I think they cut it up.
他们恨死你爸爸了
They were angry with him.
我知道  他们真的恨死他了
I know that. They were real mad with him.
如果你愿意  我还有些东西给你看
I can show you some other things, too. If you want to see more.
-好啊  -好
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-你怎么不戴上这副眼镜呢  -不
- Why don't you put the glasses on? - Nah.
他一定是想把这留给你的
For sure, he would have said they were left there for you.
没错
No doubt.
如果你愿意  就戴上试试吧
Put them on, if you want. Go on.
-什么  -听我的  戴上吧
- Yeah? - Put them on. Come on. I'll tell you.
对了
Yeah.
这就对了
-是吗  -是啊  就像他回来了一样
- Yeah? - Yeah. You're calling him back.
喂
You.
詹森
Jason!
詹...森
Jaaaasooon.
听我说
Let me talk to you.
听着  上次的事
Look man, I want to say I'm sorry
我真的很抱歉
about what happened earlier alright.
我不否认  我就是个混蛋
I was a dick. I won't deny it.
你弄丢了我的钱
You lost my money.
好吧  就这样吧
Alright. Like that's, I think
我已经把该说的都说了
that's all I need to do to fucking say, alright.
我只是想平息这件事
But I'm willing to fucking squash it, okay.
如果你愿意  就让它过去吧
If you need to squash it. I need to squash it.
那件事真的对不起  哥们
I said I'm sorry, brother. I meant that shit.
你觉得呢
Whatcha thinking?
好吧
Okay.
-你同意吗  -好吧
- You dig? - Okay.
-我们和好了吗  -当然
- We good? - Alright.
伙计  伙计  听着
Dude, dude, yeah listen. I ah...
今晚我要在我爸那儿办一个派对
I'm having a fucking party at my pop's place tonight.
哥们  别管你老爸了  一起来玩吧
Dude, your pops is fucking off the chandy, come along.
对不起  哥们  我去不了
Ah I can't do that, man. I'm sorry.
为什么
Why?
今晚不行
Can't make it tonight.
你有家事要处理吗
What, you got family stuff you gotta do?
-不是  我有别的事  -不行
- No, but I got stuff I gotta do. - Nah.
你想和好  对吗
You want to squash it right?
-我们已经和好了  -那你今晚必须来
- We squashed it. - So than come tonight.
好吧  你这么想让我去吗
Alright, you want me to come to your party tonight?
-是这样吗  -我希望你能来
- Is that what you want? - I want you to come to my party.
-好吧  晚上见  -好的  等等
- Cool, I'll see you tonight. - Alright, hold up.
-好了  晚上见  -等等
帮我个小忙  哥们  帮我搞点药来
Do me a favor, B. Bring some Oxys alright.
-我们就和好了  -不行  伙计
- Then we're straight. - No, man.
你说什么  不行  你得补偿我
What do you mean, no? You gotta make it correct.
再见了  哥们
See ya, man.
不不  你不能...  别别
No,no,no,no,no, you're not seeing....no,no, no, no,
好了  晚上见
I'll see you, okay!
不能这样
We ain't seeing shit.
你晚上一定要过来  好吧
You come tonight. Yes.
记得给我带药  好吧
You copping my Oxys. Yes.
-明白吗  -好吧  还不错
- You got it? - Alright, sounds good.
真他妈是个好主意
Alright, sounds like a fucking plan.
那玩意儿可不值500美元
It don't gotta be $500 worth, you know.
喂  J
Yo, J!
抬起头来  哥们
Keep your head up, bro!
请稍等
I'll be right back.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
臭小子  你他妈的干什么
Hey kid, the fuck you doing?
你这个小混球  滚回来
You little motherfucker! Get back here!
你搞到了
You made it.
谁想来嗑点药
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Who wants some fucking Oxy?
这儿  给你  给你  来
There it is. Here we go. Here we go. There we go. Hello.
谁还没有  伸出手来
Who ain't gotta em? All you gotta hold your fucking hands out.
放纵一下
Go crazy.
这个人是谁
Who, who is that?
-这是AJ的爸爸吗  -我想是的
- Is that AJ's dad? - I think so.
你没事吧
Are you feeling alright?
你还好吗
You okay?
有些事情你得向我解释一下
You got something you need to tell me.
你有什么要说的吗
What do you gotta tell me?
你他妈的把我当猴耍吗
Huh, you think I'm fucking stupid?
-滚出去  -你他妈的以为我...
- Get the fuck outta here. - You think I'm fucking...
-滚出去  -你把我当傻子了吗
- Get the fuck outta here! - You think I'm stupid?
滚出去  你他妈的聋了吗
Get the fuck out! You can't fucking hear?
你他妈的犯什么病呢
What's the problem with you?
你小子想干什么呢
What's your problem, man?
门就在这儿  好了  快滚吧
Here's the fucking door! Okay! There you go!
-快给我滚出去  -你他妈的混蛋
- Get the fuck out! - Fuck you, man!
詹森
Jason...
能听到我说话吗  宝贝
Can you hear me, baby?
瓦妮萨  去叫你爸爸
Vanessa, get your father.
宝贝
Baby.
你这个骗子
You're a liar.
他醒了?
He woke up?
他说什么了吗
He say something?
詹森
Hey, Jason.
你在那儿坐着等我  我去把车开过来
Why don't you sit down and wait? I'm going to get the car.
好吗
Okay?
出什么事了
What the hell happened to you?
帮帮我 好吗
Yo, I need your help, alright?
好吧  伙计  你想让我帮你什么
Yeah, man uh... Whatcha need my help for man?
我想弄把枪
I need a gun.
你要枪?
You need a gun?
进来吧
Come on in.
搞什么鬼  你他妈的想干什么
What the fuck? What the fuck are you doing?
-趴到地上去  -好  你别动
- Get on the fucking floor! - Alright, stop! Fuck!
好了
It's alright.
-明天见  -好的
- Alright, see you tomorrow. - Alright.
-你一个人吗  -怎么了
- Are you alone? - What's going on?
别看我  转过身去
Don't look at me. Turn around.
开上你的车
We're going to get in your car
你只管开车就行了
and you're just going to keep driving.
不要和我说话  不然我打爆你的头
Don't talk to me, or I'll shoot you in the back of your head.
快走
Go.
转过来
Turn around.
快转过来
你怎么进我家里去的
How did you get into my house?
AJ让我进去的
AJ let me in.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
Is he?!
把你的钱包给我
Give me your wallet.
你的钱包在哪儿
Where's your wallet?
-在我的外套里  -把你的外套给我
- It's in my jacket. - Give me your jacket.
您想要我的钱包是吗  好  给你
You want my wallet? Take the fucking wallet.
想要我的外套是吗  也给你
You want my jacket? Jacket.
跪下
Get on your knees.
你究竟把我儿子怎么了
What did you do to my son?
你给我跪下
Get on your fucking knees!
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
求你了  告诉我  我儿子没事
Please, just tell me my son's alright.
这他妈不关你儿子的事
This isn't about your fucking son.
对不起  詹森
I'm sorry, Jason.
对不起
I'm sorry.
一年多来
It was a tight race for over a year
克罗斯和凯勒曼进行了激烈的角逐
between Cross and Kellerman
在过去的一个月里  许多传闻
and then unprecedented events over the last month
对克罗斯的选举产生了不少负面影响
will lead to threaten Cross's election bid.
首先是关于未成年人在他家里聚众饮酒
First allegations of underage drinking at his house
之后他又被不明入侵者入室抢劫
and then a violent robbery from a yet unidentified intruder
他的儿子也因脑震荡住院观察
that left his son hospitalized with a concussion.
显然  克罗斯现在已经恢复竞选
Remarkably, Cross has managed to right his campaign.
正如我们所见
And now as you see,
这位地方检察官
the District Attorney has just
已赢得首席检察官的选举
won the election for Attorney General.
现在我们将直播
We will go live now as Senator Farley
法利议员的支持者致辞
prepares to address the crowds of supporters.
在艾弗里・克罗斯很小的时候
I've had the honor of knowing Avery Cross
我就认识他了
since he was a boy.
女士们  先生们  请允许我荣幸地
Ladies and gentlemen, it is my greatest honor to introduce
为大家介绍纽约州下任首席检察官
the next Attorney General of the state of New York.
艾弗里・克罗斯
Avery Cross.
AJ  快
AJ, you gotta go.
该你上台了  该你上台了
You gotta go out there. You gotta go out there.
那有一面旗子  站那个孩子旁边去
There's a flag. Go. Go where the kid is. Go.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你们
Thank you so much.
纽约州迪市亚亨路714号  妈妈收
怎么了
Yeah?
-您是兰芬德先生吗  -是的
- Mr. Renfend? - Yeah.
我给你打过电话
Hey I ah, I called you.
我说过今天会过来
Said I was going to be out here today.
对  没错
Oh, right, of course.
你来得太早了
Well, you're early.
是啊  只有一辆班车来这里
Yeah, um. There's only like one bus headed out here.
那你不是这附近的人了?
So you're not from around here huh?
不是  我要往西走
No, I'm heading out west.
可以了吗
So you ready?
-想看看吗  -当然了
- Want to go take a look at it? - Yeah.
-让我穿上衣服  -好的
- Let me just get my coat. - Alright.
车况良好
Runs great.
已经跑了不少里程了  可我保养得不错
It got a lot of miles on it. But I kept up with the maintenance.
你开个价吧
How much you want for it?
我想大概要...
Well, I was thinking I need...
五百美元吧
Five.
你以前骑过摩托吗
You ever ridden one of these before?
松林外